{
    "subject": "resource/Norman_Reid_(cricketer)",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfDeath",
    "object": "1947-06-06",
    "human_readable": "Norman Reid (cricketer) died on June 6, 1947.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.940373957157135,
            "question": "When did Norman Reid (cricketer) die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7679046988487244,
            "question": "Was Norman Reid known for playing cricket?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7664719223976135,
            "question": "Who was Norman Reid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5158379673957825,
            "question": "Is there a record of Norman Reid's cricketing achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.506155788898468,
            "question": "In what year did Norman Reid pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49037444591522217,
            "question": "Is there information available about Norman Reid's cricketing career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4543986916542053,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Norman Reid's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43432316184043884,
            "question": "What was Norman Reid's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4177822470664978,
            "question": "June 6th, 1947 is significant because...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3764340281486511,
            "question": "What other information might be available about Norman Reid?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norman Reid (cricketer) died on June 6, 1947.",
            "html": "dbpedia_789_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=June 6th, 1947 is significant because...?",
            "html": "dbpedia_789_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Norman Reid's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_789_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Norman Reid's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_789_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_789_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Specifically, document #47.txt and document #120.txt both mention that Norman Reid (cricketer) died on June 6, 1947."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document at `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_789/re-ranker-msmarco/99.txt` explicitly states that Norman Reid DSO MC (26 December 1890 \u2013 5\u20136 June 1947) was a South African cricketer who played one Test for South Africa in 1921. It also mentions his date of death as 6 June 1947, supporting the statement that Norman Reid (cricketer) died on June 6, 1947."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}